SE in there I said you know because you
know SE with the carry and I like the
pink sea I just I had to have it like
I'm like no one else is gonna have this
so so um underground radio C is what it
turned
into um because if you actually look at
my logo the word underground is actually
very grungy it's very like it's actually
got like City buildings in it if you
actually look really close and that's
what we are we're in C we're in this big
beautiful city of like flourishing
art hey what's going on folks it's Ryan
Perez here with uh bow tie creative and
this is go live and prosper uh today's
guest is a friend of mine that I've only
been friends with on Facebook so uh you
know we've been friends we we comment on
each other's post I'm like oh my God you
know this guest is uh doing so well and
I you know to be honest with you I am
you know she has been probably someone
that kind of sticks out in my mind
because I feel that um you know there's
a there's not a lot of people that are
positive on Facebook and you know as you
guys know I'm like you know almost 60
days in my positivity journey and I kind
of learn from certain folks on my
Facebook on on on those who um do
positive things so I'm pretty happy to
have um today's guest so I'm gonna ask
everybody um now that I'm live I'm just
going
to
um I'm just going to share this out
here just one
second I'm going to share this please
make sure to share this out to all your
friends and family because this is going
to be a good live um you know I've been
wanting to talk to her and um and um and
all that good stuff so one of the things
that I wanted to mention to you guys is
that we are now doing the hustle Zone
jam session uh in our um on in our group
if you go to uh hustle Zone VIP lounge
you'll be able to see the hustle own jam
session and that is only streaming on um
that's only streaming on um YouTube
because now you can you know that will
be a medium on how we raise funds to
build up um um hustle zone so you guys
can definitely go over there and be in
the Super chats and send us cashola and
we will do a nice dance for you when we
when we receive the money and we will
definitely promote your brand online so
uh make sure to share this out to all
your friends today uh and uh you'll be
able to also listen to this podcast of
go live and prosper you'll be able to
listen to it um you'll be able to listen
to it
on uh let's
see I'm drawing a blank no you'll be
able to listen to this on Google Play uh
you'll be able to listen to this on
Spotify and all of the the live
streaming networks so uh make sure to
support I'm just almost done sharing it
to my groups because I don't have my
phone in front of me so let's just go
we're share share share share share go
live and prosper perfect and we're
almost
done share it to live talk
Nation share live talk
nation and one more we're going to share
it
to podcast
podcasters so we can get some people in
here
today
okay perfect okay so today's guest um
she is a personal friend of mine um and
she is also a radio uh she is a radio
host she has her own radio station
called radio C I want you guys to give
it up for
Miss Carrie Weber how are you
doing good how are you I'm doing great
than for having me today yeah it's been
uh we we've had some tech technical
difficulties to get on this show today
so you know um hopefully nothing happens
my house doesn't get hit by lightning or
what have you uh but um but welcome to
welcome to go live and prosper we've
been doing this show for three three
years three and some maybe four years
we've been doing this show for four
years and we we people would get mad at
me if I don't ask you the first question
which is what is your story so tell us
you are how did you get to the position
that you were in right now uh and um
what were some of the you know
challenges along the
way okay big long story but we'll make
it a little bit short um so basically
I've been separated for the past couple
years and I actually started looking for
because I have to go and work and get
out there into the world yeah so I
actually started um in a cleaning
business for one of my friends that she
owns a cleaning company so she's like
hey you know car I know you need some
work why don't you come work for me and
I was like okay that's great so I was
working for her for quite a while and
then work kind of got slow so I was like
I'm going to just start looking around
so I was looking around for different
work you know the usual kind of work
sites like Facebook Marketplace um
indeed work opless you name it we just
search all over the place so I found um
a radio listing for a radio show host
and so I was like okay I'm going to just
apply why not like you you have nothing
to lose right only things to gain so I
put my resume into him and it was within
two days he got back to me and he's like
I would love to interview you and um see
if you're you know a good fit for us so
um it was actually really quite
interesting because the um address that
he sent me to was the opposite side of
the city um it was snowing like it was
one of our blizzards
it was really really horrible
outside and so I was messaging him and
I'm like I'm I'm at this address that
you sent me to for the uh interview and
I said I don't know where you guys are
like I don't see any signs I don't see
anything and he's like oh he said we
moved and I was like oh okay well I said
what's your new address and then I'll
drive out there and me to and he's like
you know he said I actually have
somebody in studio right now and he said
you know I'll I'll tell you what I said
in he said like a half an hour I'll call
you and then we'll just do it over the
phone and I said okay I said that's fair
enough you like I'm driving around the
city like a mad woman in the store
anyway so it's gave me a chance to kind
of park somewhere and actually just do a
quick interview with him so needless to
say after the interview which wasn't
even very long it was about a half an
hour um I got the job so he was very
pleased with how I was with him and
being positive and just the person that
I am I have this huge Charisma and
everything people love I'm person person
right so yeah I was like okay great so
um yeah so within the week I was into
the studio and then I started my new
career of being in radio but I was still
cleaning on the side so I was like okay
kind of doing a couple things you know
how the hustle is so it was actually
really good like it was a really good
thing um so I continued to of course you
know start in radio I started um
learning how to do interviews uh we had
a bunch of guests into the studio a
bunch of artists come in and um I
started just learning how to do
everything and I was just like this is
the greatest thing ever right and so F
like I didn't even know but recently I
had a little talk with one of my parents
and she's like you know the funny thing
is she's like when you were little you
told me that you wanted to be in radio
wow and I was like
wow like I had no idea okay and the
funny thing is yeah I know like you and
I we've been friends on Facebook for
quite a while like quite a few years
actually um but when I actually first
started Facebook I've only actually been
on there I think about seven years and
my first actual friends on there like my
first like they're you know they're not
like your friends friends but they your
your first connections right so we'll
just call them connections for now
because ideally you maybe grow into a
friendship or something so for sure um
my first friends were actually people
that were in the entertainment industry
they were actually some singers some
dancers and and some people that were
doing like they own venues or things
like that so it's actually quite
interesting that even before I had got
into it I was actually making all these
connections along the way which was kind
of like a really cool thing so and now
probably over half of them are actually
really good friends of mine which is in
itself really cool so kind of like a
whole Destiny thing one second I just
want to acknowledge some of the people
we got in the room we got Tracy Moore
she says God bless your business awesome
oh thank you so much Tracy I appreciate
that and God bless you Tracy thank you
for coming in yes and then we have to
thank you Monica Black Diamond she is a
co-host of the uh Hustle on jam session
she says hey Ryan G so awesome thank you
for being here guys that's awesome so
cool so very cool I'll connect with you
guys too definitely I'm all about
Connections really so yeah so then um I
started doing the whole radio thing I
just loved it learned like met so many
people been to a few events here and
there and
then I was continually trying to bring a
lot of creative ideas to the
owner and I was saying you know we
should do this and we should do that
like I have so many great ideas can we
just do this and this and this and I
felt like there were a lot of
restrictions um like sometimes he's like
well yeah we can go live on location but
we're actually we can't go there for
whatever reason or I know things kind of
came up and then I had you know great
ideas for like helping him brand things
or arti in or things like that and um
some of my ideas were just kind of shot
down and I was like okay well you know
it's your own business you run things
how you do we are we all do that right
right so you're not going to step on
toes you're not going to do whatever um
but this I kind of noticed it was
probably like eight months ago that I
started seeing it and then my friends
kind of brought it up to me they're like
hey car you know um you're so great at
this and and things and they're like you
know it's too bad like
it's not flourishing enough for you as
as what you really want it to be so I
was like yeah you know like I don't know
so they're like I kind of had this
manifest of doing my own thing and I was
like well I don't really know how to
kind of start it I was just kind of like
um we'll see so I was kind of like
writing ideas down um getting some
information from a few people here and
there so this is kind of how the radio C
actually kind of like I said manifested
in a little way so I was like okay well
so I kind of hung on to the idea had all
these little notes written down and I
was like okay well and I was starting to
write down the actual connections that I
have who could I interview who could I
do this or do I want to just do artists
and I thought you know like I know so
many people just on Facebook never mind
Instagram okay just and the people in my
life that I've got other connections
with so I was like well why not why not
Branch out to entrepreneurs like
yourself why not Branch out to dancers
like I was in dance for a little while
and I met a great choreographers um the
owner of the studio that's Tara Wilson
with post Studios shout out to her
because she's amazing amazing woman um
changing so many lives like so these
people that have changed my life over
the past couple years I want to bring
them and and share their stories while
I'm sharing my story so that everyone
can kind of connect and kind of like
well they understand where I'm coming
from what I'm trying to do and I just
like want to share it so as I started
branding everything because I'm like
okay I need to like a regular business
you have to get your name out there get
known and how about do you do this so I
was like well okay first of all it's
obvious you need like a logo you need a
name things like that so I was floating
around with some ideas and one of them
was radio seat so I was like well that's
really cool and for me hi Tracy she's
back she's
awesome um for me pink I love pink pink
is my favorite color and I thought
that's got to be part of my brand was
the pink because that's just I love it
it's such a vibrant color I'm a vibrant
person I thought you know this is
something that's going to really work
and it's just it makes me happy to wear
it it makes me have you know it looks G
on me whatever um but it just in general
like it's such a summer fun color and
everyone loves it so I thought you know
it's something that's gonna be bold and
standout so um I met with one of my
friends um her name is Alexandra serado
she's amazing she's also an entrepreneur
and I'm going to shout out to her as
well because she's not only my best
friend um we were neighbors for probably
almost 10 years um so we got really
close over the past while like so closed
like we share so much um not only are we
just best friends neighbors but we also
I help her with her rescue so she runs
tales of the Misunderstood um Vol like
it's a a rescue for dogs volunteer basis
I'll go in and I'll help her um walk
dogs or take dog clients overnight
things like that
um to help her out so um kind of not
really in return but because I've been
helping her she's like you know she's
into the business stuff and I was like
okay well like I really kind of need
help like you know you don't want to
admit it but we all need help starting
things up so she's like okay she's like
you know pulls me aside she's like care
she's like I've got some ideas and she's
like We're going to make this work and I
was like okay so for Christmas it was a
huge
huge surprise and I was like I literally
I cried um but she like brought me to
her house she's like I got something for
you here and I was like okay great like
I come pick it up whatever she's like
okay yeah and she's like it's upstairs
my office and I was like okay sure
whatever you know maybe she was busy in
her office doing things on the computer
like she always does and and that's fine
like you know it is what it is so I was
like okay this is kind of strange in a
way but anyway she just goes come on in
take a seat and she says but you have to
close your eyes and I was like
okay like kind of like kind of weird but
I'm like okay just go with it um so
she's like open your eyes and there on
her computer screen was the logo she
made up for me and I was like this is I
I was in tears and I was like this is
just it's amazing like thank you so much
it was like the best gift ever and Not
only was it the logo but she started the
web page for me too so I was like this
this is just like it just everything
just flowed and it just happened right
so and I just and I literally couldn't
forward the process um because I
actually had to leave the radio station
so like that was kind of thing I just
having like somebody say well they
didn't like my ideas or didn't like this
or didn't like that it just puts in
perspective like okay well you know what
I can do this on my own or go somewhere
else where someone will appreciate my
efforts and why not like you have
nothing to lose so as they say you know
one door closes the other one opens and
I've had so many doors open and Clos for
me the past couple years and it's just
been so amazing and it's just so that's
kind of like how it all started to
flourish but um going back to the
logo um
so I've got I'm actually now part
partnered up with EVO King
management um Natasha shout out to you
you're amazing Daniel Southerland okay
you guys are so amazing they decided
that they wanted to work with me and so
we've been playing around with some
ideas and she's like you know um I
Googled up
radio and she said there's actually
quite a few out there and like you go on
Twitter Instagram like there's a few
there and I was like oh um I said okay
well let's think of some other ideas and
what we can do because when you're in
this
industry as an entrepreneur as somebody
that's going to be working with artists
or bigger venues things like that you
have to stand out right you can't just
be like this little tiny logo on a
picture on a poster and be like oh
that's just another radio C who cares so
you want to have something big and bold
and beautiful and this big product that
everyone wants to share right so that's
that's what you know like I'm a very
kind of low-key person but I find like
when I want to do a project it's massive
like I want everyone to be like hey this
is amazing and I want them to be a part
of it because that's just the joy of
what you do and I just there's so much
joy in what I'm doing now so I'm just so
thrilled so um Natasha and I were kind
of playing around with some ideas and
we're like okay well why don't you do
like Urban or underground or something
and urban underground or you know and I
was was like yeah but I want to keep the
radio c in there I said you know because
you know see the carry and I like the
pink SE I just I had to have it like I'm
like no one else is gonna have this so
so um underground radio C is what it
turned
into um because if you actually look at
my logo the word underground is actually
very grungy it's very like it's actually
got like City buildings in it if you
actually look really close and that's
what we are we're in Calgary we're in
this big beautiful city of like
flourishing artists and flourishing
entrepreneurs and it's like you know
let's let's just build this let's just
make it bigger and right that's what
it's got to be when you're branding you
gotta brand it right right it's It's
gotta be huge right so and that's what I
wanted I wanted something big something
B Something Beautiful going hey this is
the city we're in this is this is how it
is and Underground can be expressed in
many different ways so that's why for me
I decided like I'm not just G to have
the underground artists I want to have
you know people that are in dance or
other musicians um you know just get
their word out there like there's
underground businesses like it's not
just as they think Underground Music
like there's so much more that can be
brought into light and I think it's so
important that people can actually
collaborate build together and be like
you know there's too much um like I just
see floating around like you said the
negativity on Facebook and you're just
like like why are you guys jealous of
each other why are you guys like just
bashing each other like why is there
this negative feed and you're like come
on guys like we're on Facebook most of
us and like I used to use Facebook not
because I wasn't even like I didn't have
business before anything but I used it
as an outlet to kind of like Get
positivity in my life I had had friends
on there that I actually wanted to meet
like eventually Ryan you and I we will
meet eventually but you know but for now
this is a good step um but yeah so like
a lot of the artists like I said that I
had actually um started like that we
became friends in the very beginning
like seven years ago six years ago all
these people now
are like I said they're coming into my
life I'm actually you know having this
friendship relationship with them and
I'm like wow you guys are like so
amazing not just on the screen like you
guys are like legit amazing people out
there like you're on the stage you're
teaching people you're like there's such
a huge purpose like everyone has and
it's just like it was so amazing to
actually see it and so I went from just
like the scroll of every day going oh
well okay they're doing events and I'm
not there um it was a little bit
negative at first because you're like I
really want to be a part of it but you
don't know how and when I was in this
situation where it wasn't necessarily
healthy relationship things like that it
was very you know four walls let's just
put it that way yeah so you know you
can't really be yourself you can't
really do go and express anything you
can't really live in a way so I got out
of that in a very good timing and um
then I got to actually you know meet
these people and start actually learning
about them and and going you know like I
don't know how it all came to be but it
just all just kind of like the universe
brought everyone kind of together like I
thank god seriously like every day for
like everybody that's in my life
everyone that's crossed paths with me if
they taught me a lesson or whatever it
is you know um it's just been it's been
an incredible ride like and it's just
for me like I'm looking at it and I'm
going like just literally from December
is when I I made my page up on Facebook
and put my first little Post in there
and I was like oh my Facebook page and
oh yeah right and then now it's like
okay last night I actually put up that
beginning March 1 I am now taking
bookings and I'm doing interviews and I
was like this is like only in two less
than two months yeah it's like it's it's
growing and now I've got a couple
Partners so I've got Evo King management
like I said shout out to them that's
Natasia pet and Daniel Sutherland and
I'm also working with another partner
who's not local um but he's actually
very good friend of mine we too started
off kind of like on social media um we
grew into huge friends over the past few
years um he owns his own kickboxing
Studio out in High River
he used to work in Calgary um but their
business got shut down and that was um
just only actually a few months ago as
well because we were going to start
doing this kind of stuff together so
we're actually going to be podcasting
together um I'm actually meeting him
this afternoon and we're going to start
like this huge like podcasting
positivity motivation how to go from
like your little Journeys along the way
because everyone's got a even a fitness
journey or a mindset Journey or right
whatever it is so we're not going to
just talk Health but it's going to be
bigger like it's going to be like you
know how can we help you to maybe grow
your business too like it's it's gonna
be it's gonna be huge like and so these
are just the two partners I have right
now um but I I do I want to work with
other people like crazy like I'm just
it's so fun it's so fantastic and I love
people's creative ideas and I love just
like um another thing too like I'm sort
of offering with my business this too is
that people always say I'm kind of like
this Matchmaker and I was like
okay so I've actually not just match
made people like relationships but I've
only done a couple of those proud to say
I think they're still going um yeah
that's awesome but anyway um not just
that but musically too I've actually met
a few artists and they're like hey you
know you interviewed um so one of the
persons I'm going to be interview soon
is um his name is Kay The Chosen he's an
artist and he messaged me like a little
while ago he kind of heard about me and
he's like you know I heard you did this
interview with tiny wings back a few
months ago in the radio like in the
studio and I said yeah I said I I did
and she's like amazing and just
wonderful person and she's got this
bubbly personality and just like amazing
music she's started as a poet and now
she's a RPP and like people have these
stories like so and so he's like you
know um he's like do you think you can
actually kind of like maybe hook us
up and I was like you know what I said
absolutely I said you know I'm tasing
dreams let's chase your dreams why not
so I want to make sure like that
continues like I know like Natasha and I
were going to be swapping a lot of
artists together that's kind of like
what we want to do is be able to be like
okay I interview this person you can
interview them they're so great and
we
oh
sorry just unexpected phone call uh okay
sorry someone just interrupted guess
it's live that's what happens right for
sure um yeah so I just want to be able
to connect them and just be like this is
just amazing like this person's amazing
you could work with so and so so that's
also going to be part of my services
like I just want to be able to connect
people and I just want to have that Vibe
and then promote music too because not
enough people are like maybe they're on
Instagram or they're than they're on
Facebook right like everyone's got their
thing like you said you know Twitter
like who's using that anymore right yeah
but I'm trying I'm really I'm really
trying to Branch out my whole social
media to more than just the two um I
think it's really important um to kind
of really there's so many more people
out there like we just don't even know
it's so important so um yeah so I just
want to be able to bring more people in
and connect more people and then do like
music promo I'll promote like I said
I'll be sharing this and I'll be
promoting your business I want to
promote like so many other people that
have come into my life
because they helped me through one of my
R really really rough times in my life
like it's not just rough it was a really
rough time and I wanted to to be able to
just you know give that love back and be
like you know right um that's kind of
who I am you can ask anyone like they
they give me 20 bucks and I'm like here
here's like a 100 okay like I feel bad
you know like you know rough situations
but I I try and give back a 100 fold
like people come over and they want to
help me with something I'm like okay you
know what I got like two days let me
come help you with something you know
like
um my best friend she will uh you
know let's see I don't hoping I'm not
paused here no you're not pause okay
sorry I just keep getting this phone
call I don't know why but anyway um so
yeah so like you know my best friend and
my neighbor who's you know she works
with the dogs and you know she needed a
break and so I said to her I said you
know she always gets people to watch her
house or watch her dogs and I keep
telling her I'm like Alex I said I'll
come over and watch the house for you
like I have no problem doing this for
you like just just trust me you know
like she's like yeah but my dogs aren't
you know there's like this whole routine
and they got to be fed this way and put
in their little kenel this way and I was
like okay I said I I could do that like
it's okay i' I have no issues so finally
after so many years um she went away for
two weeks which I'm so thankful she got
away and I got to go over and help her
with her house and did the dogs and all
that kind of stuff and it was just like
finally she can see that you know I want
to help her I want to repay and help all
these people and so that's kind of
that's kind of who I am I'm just like a
consistent you know I think sometimes I
give too much and that's probably a big
fault of mine but I try to you know I
just want to reciprocate like that's
just kind of who I am you're helping me
I'm going to help you and that's who it
is but um I've learned
indefinitely um I've been taken
advantage of too many times so that's
kind of one thing that I've really
learned over you know the past probably
five six even 10 years of my life um
that's something that people are taking
advantage of you so yeah so that's just
one thing but yeah so I'm just really
really thrilled to be able to be doing
this and um
help people out and it's just it's just
gonna be so insane and so incredible
awesome so this huge Journey I'm just
like I'm so excited and
overwhelmed well that well that that's
awesome and now I can't hear you oh no
oh you can't hear me this happened
that's probably why hold on let's while
she gets that figured out um you know
what a great story so let's just read
the um comments in the comment section
um so Tracy wow you've had um so she
says when God is for you who can be
against you yes I agree with you with
that um she says I am one of the
underground unique businesses out there
well we'll have to get you on on our
show and if anyone's looking for Logos
or Graphics design or um web design or
what have you just let me know um
comment below and and I will contact you
after the show
uh and then Tracy says I'm a praise
worship a dancer singer fashion designer
uh awesome
and she says Satan get out of the way
yes so we're gonna bring hopefully um
the the audio issues are still working I
can see let's see is how is the
audio hey you can hear me again I think
we just have technical difficulties but
I can't are you now okay well you know I
I I'm gonna I'm going to thank you for
um I I'm G to thank you for coming in uh
uh Carrie I really appreciate your story
I think that was an amazing story and
folks if you guys want you guys can um
let's see here you
can uh uh uh you can find her at
underground radio under- C and she's on
Instagram and then she's also on Twitter
so make sure to check her out I think
that um you know she's an amazing person
I really appreciate her coming on to the
show I know we were having some
technical um issues and difficulties and
and hopefully she'll come back as a
guest or maybe I could be a guest on her
show I don't know so um you know either
way thank you guys all for joining um
here today uh and I will talk to you
guys soon so peace out and make sure to
follow us on YouTube on everywhere uh
we're YouTube We're on Facebook we're on
Instagram um follow us a follow us at
hustle Zone TV and you know we do have a
website um coming soon which will have
all these videos and all this good stuff
so I am super super super super excited
um you know that you guys are all you
know embracing Us in open arms and of
course this this broadcast is brought to
you by
ww. boyc creative.com so b o WTI
K uh k r a t i
v.com and uh welcome to the hustle Zone
talk to you guys later
bye
e
e for